Juciano C Barbosa

Itatiba, São Paulo, Brazil



juciano@outlook.com.br



linkedin.com/in/juciano-c-barbosa

Summary

I'm a software developer, currently working with front-end technologies, like ReactJS and Angular. I also have experience with NodeJS and other technologies like Docker Docker-Compose Git.

You can find me on Github https://github.com/Jucian0

You can read my posts on Dev.to https://dev.to/jucian0

Experience

Senior Software developer Frontend

Sensedia

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Work as a Front-End developer.

- Developing new features, improving the product, and fixing issues.
- Developing internal design system and library components.
- Onboarding new employees.

Technologies:

- ReactJS (Redux, Styled-Components, NextJS)
- AngularJS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Docker/Docker Compose
- Git

Middle Software developer Frontend

Sensedia

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Work as a Front-End developer.

- Developing new features, improving the product, and fixing issues.
- Developing internal design system and library components.
- Onboarding new employees.

Technologies:

- ReactJS (Redux, Styled-Components, NextJS)
- AngularJS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Docker/Docker Compose
- Git

Junior Software developer Frontend

Sensedia

Sep 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Work as a Front-End developer.

- Developing new features, improving the product, and fixing issues.

Technologies:

- ReactJS (Redux, Redux saga)
- AngularJS
- Javascript
- Git

Intern

Sensedia

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018 (7 months)

Work as a Front-End developer.

- Developing new features, improving the product, and fixing issues.

Technologies:

- AngularJS
- Javascript

Software Developer

Juciano

Nov 2015 - Nov 2017 (2 years 1 month)

Developing websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.

- Javascript
- PHP
- Wordpress
- CSS

Education



USE Universidade São Francisco

Analise de Desenvolvimento de Sistemas, Computer Software Engineering 2015 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications

- ReactJS Redux Udemy
- NodeJS Udemy UC-ITVJ87G6
- **Web Development** Udemy UC-317YO55U

Skills

Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) • Bitbucket • AngularJS • Angular Material • docker • REST APIs • Swagger API • css • Pipelines • Angular